Yuuki-chan, what do you think?
ゆうきちゃん、どう?
picture?
え?
amazing.
すごい
That's amazing, so beautiful.
すごいね、綺麗
There are fish.
魚いる
It's cute.
可愛いね
A weak damselfish.
駆弱スズメダイ
cute.
可愛い
What is the name of this?
これとの名前?
Weak driving.
駆弱
Is it fading?
褪色になってるんですかね?
Yuuki-chan's face has turned extremely yellow.
ゆうきちゃんの顔がすげえ黄色になってる
Sparkling.
キラキラ
This fish looks delicious.
なんかうまそうな魚いるよ、これ
Can't you eat this?
これ食えんじゃない?
this.
これ
Hey, this is my uncle.
え、これおじさんだっす
uncle?
おじさん?
Uncle, dog.
おじさん、犬
Really?
ほんとに?
My name is Uncle.
おじさんって名前なんだ
It's my uncle's fish.
おじさんの魚だ
looks delicious.
美味しそう
Isn't this Nemo?
これニモじゃねえの?
different?
違う?
this.
これ
Do you like animals?
動物好き?
Yuuki-chan.
ゆうきちゃん
動物?
I love animals.
動物好きです
I like it.
好きなんだ
What do you like?
何が好きなの?
It's a dog.
犬です
dog?
犬?
You look like a cat.
あんた猫っぽい顔してるけど
lie?
嘘?
People say I look like a dog?
犬っぽいって言われます?
yes.
そう
What is your personality?
性格が?
surely.
確かに
Friendly person.
人懐っこやもん
Jellyfish.
ク ラゲー
Isn't the jellyfish cute?
クラゲー可愛くね?
cute.
可愛い
Isn't this how you die?
こうやって死んでない?
I'm alive.
生きてます
Are you alive?
生きてるの?
Wow.
うわ
Isn't this kind of thing poisonous?
こんなの毒あるんじゃない?
poison?
毒?
This is poisonous.
毒あるよ、これ
Suba's clover-like mark is cute.
スバーのクロバーみたいなマークが可愛いですよ
which one?
どれ?
Jellyfish?
クラゲーの?
Jellyfish.
ク ラゲーの
surely.
確かに
long time no see?
久しぶり?
It's been a while since I've been here.
久しぶりに来ました
It's so cute.
すごい可愛いな
What about chocolate?
チョコは?
Is there a place where you can take pictures like this?
こんなって撮れるとこないですか?
No.
ないです
strange.
おかしい
strange?
おかしい?
Even though these guys are in an aquarium, there's something lively about them.
こいつら水槽なのになんかイキイキしてる
Huh, what is that?
え、何それ?
scared.
怖い
You've got a bad guy.
や ばいやついたね
This is scary.
これ恐ろしいな
Is there a sea?
海入ってる?
What would you do if it came right in front of you?
それ目の前に来たらどうする?
Makes me nostalgic.
懐かせる
Make you feel nostalgic?
懐かせる?
Makes me nostalgic.
懐かせる
Hello.
こんにちは
Yuki-chan.
ゆきちゃん
You're really cute.
あなた、まじで可愛いっすね
No, thank you very much.
いや、ありがとうございます
It's really cute.
本当に可愛いわ
Celebrity class cuteness.
芸能人クラスの可愛さ
That's not it.
それはないです
This good character.
この性格の良さ
Yuki-chan is popular, right?
ゆきちゃん、モテるでしょ?
No, I'm not that popular.
いや、そんなモテないですよね
Is that so?
そうなの?
I think it's about normal.
普通ぐらいだと思います
How many people have you dated so far?
今まで何人くらい付き合ったことあった?
Are there only two people?
2人しかいないの?
It feels like one person is the longest.
1人が長目みたいな感じ
That's right.
そう なんだ
That's one thing.
1つなんだね
He is the type of person who is quite easy to become addicted to.
結構、依存しやすいタイプです
That's right.
そうなんだ
From a man's point of view, it's great.
男からしたら最高だね
Having such a cute girl depend on me.
こんな可愛い子に依存してもらって
Don't you have a boyfriend now?
今、彼氏いないの?
I'm not there right now.
今はいないです
It's a waste.
もったいないね
Why don't you make it?
なんでつくんないの?
boyfriend.
彼氏
I haven't come across many people.
あまり出会えたことないんですよ
now.
今は
That's right.
そう なんだ
It's a waste.
もったいないね
Uncle, I almost want to run for office.
おじさん、立候補したいぐらいだもん
2 people with experience?
経験人数2人?
that's right.
そうです
Two people?
2人か
There aren't many.
少ないね
Surprisingly.
意外に
That's what it is.
そんなもんですよね
perhaps.
多分
There may be many children who are not as cute as Yuki-chan.
ゆきちゃんより可愛くない子の方が多いかもしれないね
No, no.
いや いや
Yuki-chan, mask.
ゆきちゃんさ、マスクさ
Shall I take it?
とってみようか
So cute.
めっちゃ可愛い
close.
近い
It's close, isn't it?
近いでしょ
It's close, that is.
近いです、それは
Is it near?
近 いか
Yeah.
うん
Her skin is also very white.
すごい肌も真っ白だね
snow.
ゆき
It's like snow.
ゆきみたい
It's the same as the name.
名前と一緒だね
Don't you walk outside anymore?
外はもう歩かないの?
I walk outside to avoid the sun.
外は、 結構日差しを避けて歩きますね
I see, somewhere.
そっか、どっか
I see.
なるほどね
Yuki-chan, please stand up for a moment.
ゆきちゃん、ちょっと立ってみてよ
It's very thin.
すごい細いね
Are you on a diet?
ダイエットしてるの?
No, I don't really go on a diet.
いや、あんまり ダイエット絶対はしてない
That's right.
そうなんだ
It's so stylish.
すごいスタイリーじゃん
No, the style isn't that good.
いや、スタイルそんなよくないんですよ
This is amazing.
すごいこれは
Will other girls get angry?
他の女の子怒られちゃうよ?
If I were to say this.
こう言ってたら
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
No, I'm nervous.
いや、緊張します
I will.
するよね
The third person in my life.
人生で3人目が
surely.
確かに
Wow, I'm going to do something naughty today.
すごい今日エッチなことするけど
Are you naughty?
エッチですか?
terrible.
やばい
It might be dangerous.
やばいかもしれない
That's terrible.
やばいね
When I see something this cute, it really gets me excited.
こんだけ可愛いとね、 すごいテンション上がります
Looks like some sort of idol.
どっかのアイドルいそうだもんね
No, there are no idols.
いやいや、アイドルはいない
Are you a drinking slope recruiter?
飲み坂募集者なの?
Drinking slope.
飲み坂
It's impossible, it's impossible.
無理です無理です
I want you to look back.
後 ろ向いてみてほしい
How many centimeters tall?
身長何センチ?
He is 155 cm tall.
身長155センチです
155 cm?
155センチか
It looks taller, I'm kind of tall.
もっと高く見えるね、なんか身長
Why?
なんでだろう?
なんでですかね
Quite small.
結構小さめ
My face is small.
顔がちっちゃいんだよ
close.
近い
You have a small face.
顔がちっちゃいもんね
You're only half of me.
俺の半分しかないじゃん
No, no.
いやいや
face.
顔
amazing.
すごい
Are you doing something that makes your face look small?
なんか小顔の何かやってるの?
But I do force my face to look smaller and give myself a morning massage.
でも結構小顔強制とか、朝マッサージとかします
That's right.
そうなんだ
I'm sure you're being considerate.
やっぱ気使ってるんだね
It's easy to get swollen from the start.
すごいむくみやすくて元から
I go there quite a bit.
結 構行ったりします
Yeah, it's not swollen at all, right?
そう、 全くむくんでないでしょ?
No, I'm swollen today.
いや、今日むくんでます
Are you swollen?
むくんでます?
I usually lose my face.
顔なくなっちゃうじゃん、普段
No, about 1.1 times the usual amount.
いや、いつもの1.1倍ぐらい
1.1 times?
1.1倍?
It's about 1/10th bigger.
10分の1ぐらいで大きいってことね
It's small enough though.
十分ちっちゃいけどな
Take off the gray one above.
この上の灰色のやつ、ちょっと脱いでみて
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing to take it off.
脱ぐのは恥ずかしい
I've never been photographed before.
撮られたことなくないもんね
This is even cuter when you take it off.
脱いだらもっと可愛いじゃん、これ
Is it true?
本当ですか?
She's a serious idol.
ガチアイドルやん
This looks like an idol costume.
こういうのアイドル衣装でありそう
It kind of looks like they're doing a capicap dance.
なんかキャピキャピダンス踊ってそうだもん
I really can't dance.
本当にダンスできないんですよ
This one was cute, so I'll try it again.
今のも可愛かったし、もう一回やって
That's really bad.
め っちゃ下手くそ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Yuki dance appeared.
ゆきダンス出た
Yuki dance?
ゆきダンス?
At Henyo Henyo.
ヘニョヘニョで
Great cleaning experience.
すごい清掃感
How many cup breasts do you have?
胸何カップあるの?
My breasts are only B cup size.
胸はBカップしかないです
Small boobs.
ちっぱいな
It's small.
ちっぱいです
Small breasts are cute too, right?
ちっぱいのも可愛いよね?
No, just a little more.
いや、もうちょい
It would be just fine if there were about 2 more cups.
あと2カップぐらいあったらちょうどいい
It's okay, have small breasts.
いいじゃん、ちっぱいで
no.
いや
Did you know that small breasts are more sensitive?
ちっぱいのが感度いいって知ってた?
Is that so?
そうなんですか?
Maybe it will happen.
そうなるんかも
That's right.
そうだよ
Can you just turn around?
そんま後ろ向いてみ?
Try lifting your skirt slowly.
スカートゆっくり上げてみて
Show me your pants, pants.
パンツ見せてよ、パンツ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
I could see it a little.
ちょっと見えた
Isn't it a little transparent?
なんかちょっと透けてない?
pants.
パンツ
picture?
え?
It's not transparent.
透けてない
I can see the roundness of her butt.
お尻の丸が見える
It goes well with white.
白に合うね
I guess it's mostly white.
結構基本的に白が多いかも
It opens really quickly.
ほんとパッと開くね
Show me everything.
全部見せて
Yeah.
うん
What a beautiful butt.
すごい綺麗なお尻
No, her butt isn't very pretty.
いや、お尻はあまり綺麗じゃない
It's beautiful.
綺麗だよ
My legs are short enough.
足の短いのが足りない
Isn't it short?
短くないの?
Only two people have touched this.
これが2人しか触ってない
Butt?
お尻か
It's rare and valuable.
希少価値高いね
It's rare.
レアだよな
Look here?
こっち見てごらん?
Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃん
Unbutton your shirt.
シャツのボタン開けてさ
Brajami-chan.
ブラジャミちゃん
I've wanted to touch it ever since.
さっきからずっと触りたかった
Slowly, slowly.
ゆっくりだ、ゆっくり
It's so cute.
すっごい可愛いもんね
This smile.
この笑顔
Erotic.
エロ
Isn't the shape so beautiful?
形すごい綺麗じゃない?
No, this is Brajami-chan.
いや、これはブラジャミちゃん
copper?
どう?
This has been taken.
これ撮られちゃってる
No, very little.
いや、めっちゃちょっと
It's so embarrassing.
めちゃめちゃ恥ずかしい
Are you confused?
ハタフタしちゃう?
That's amazing.
すごいよね
Pure white.
真っ白で
Kuro-chan, you're so excited today.
クロちゃん、今日は興奮しちゃってるでしょ
terrible.
やばい
It's too cute.
可愛すぎだ
Well, let's start with these breasts.
じゃあ、こっちのおっぱいから
Let's go to Chikuri.
ちくりにいっちゃおう
Chikuri?
ち くり?
It's a little bit boring.
ちくりはちょっと
Small.
ちっちゃい
No, just a little.
いや、ちょっと
Good luck, it's embarrassing.
がんばって、恥ずかしい
So beautiful.
すごい綺麗
No, please don't upload it.
いや、アップにしないでください
I'll just upload it.
ちょうどアップにするよ
No, it's not good, really.
いや、ちょっとダメでしょ、本当に
It's close, that's for sure.
近いよ、それ、絶対
She has such beautiful breasts.
こんな綺麗なおっぱい持って
It's not pretty.
綺麗じゃない
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
Yeah.
うん
That too.
そっちも
It's open.
オープンしちゃって
It would be great to have an idol like this.
こんなアイドルいたら最高だね
An idol who shows off her breasts.
おっぱい見せてくれるアイドル
Aren't your breasts about to wake up?
おっぱい起きそうじゃない?
Huh?
えっ?
Isn't it about D?
Dぐらいあんじゃないの?
There isn't.
ないですよ
B or C?
BかCか
I have to ask Kuro-chan to suck me and capine me later.
あとでクロちゃんにしゃぶって、 カピネしてもらわないと
Well then, come on.
じゃあ、さあ
Try sitting here.
ここ座ってみてね
Boredom falls and boredom falls.
退屈が落ちて退屈が
So cute.
かわいいなぁ
Open your legs a little.
この足ちょっと開いて
More, more, more.
もっともっともっと
Fully open.
全開
Full throttle?
全開は?
This is full throttle.
これが全開
That's full throttle.
それが全開だね
My uncle and I helped out later and went all out.
おじさんと一緒に後で手伝って思いっきり全開
Do it again.
もう一度やって
I can't wait to see her pussy.
早くマンコ見たくてたまらないね
No, no.
いやいや
Is your pussy embarrassing?
マンコ恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよね
It's embarrassing, but I'll show it to you.
恥ずかしいけど見せちゃうか
Kuro-chan was embarrassed so I helped her.
クロちゃん恥ずかしいから手伝ったんよ
You took your pussy off.
マンコ脱がしたね
Did you take it off?
脱いちゃった?
Were you taken off?
脱がされた?
I was taken off my clothes.
脱がされました
Wait, I'm a little embarrassed.
えー待って恥ずかしくてちょっと
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
No way.
やだ
Kuro-chan was the one who flew.
フライングしたのクロちゃん
No, wait.
やだー待って
I've never thought of a hand like this as a hindrance.
こんな手が邪魔だと思ったことない
It's not pretty.
綺麗じゃないです
Isn't it beautiful?
あんま綺麗じゃないの?
Well then, let me check.
じゃあちょっと確認させて
No, not anymore.
いやもう
Please let me confirm what it is.
何だよ確認させてください
Please melt this hand.
この手溶かしてください
Very bad.
めっちゃダメ
No, no.
やだやだ
Amazing pink.
すごいピンク
A very beautiful pink.
めっちゃ綺麗なピンク
So beautiful.
すごい綺麗
This cute pussy.
こんな可愛いこのマンコ
Is it the best?
最高なのかな?
Try opening this pussy yourself.
自分でさ、 このマンコのビラビラ 開いてみしてください
Try opening it.
開いてみ
Is it like this?
こういうの?
I can see everything more clearly.
もっとバッと全部見える
oh yeah.
そうそう
Wow, your pussy is so small.
うわマンコちっちゃいね
It's embarrassing to be so close.
ちょっと近いと恥ずかしい
It's so close it's embarrassing.
すごい近くて恥ずかしいね
Kuro-chan.
クロちゃん
Yuki-chan, you're shy, because your hands are the most annoying thing in the world.
ゆきちゃん恥ずかしがってさ、 手が世界一邪魔だから、
I opened Kuro-chan with a little manual effort.
ちょっと手動かして、 クロちゃん開いたの
Come in here, this too.
ここに入って、 こっちも
I'll open it.
開くよ
Please open it as much as you can.
思いっきり開いてください
You can see all the way to the back.
奥まで映ってるよ
Try hollowing it out.
くりむいてみ
You like chestnuts, right?
くり好きでしょ?
dislike?
嫌い?
I don't like it.
嫌だよ
We're looking at the world.
俺らが世界一見てる
Stick your butt out further.
お尻もっと前に突き出して
I'll even put it on my feet.
足上にも上げちゃう
I'll raise it more.
もっと上げちゃう
Kuro-chan, open it up as much as you can.
クロちゃん思いっきり開いて
One person to the deepest part.
一人一番奥まで
I don't like it, I don't like it.
嫌だ嫌だ
I can see it.
見える見える
The butthole is also visible.
お尻の穴も映ってる
It's a bit no good.
ちょっとダメです
Tighten it up a bit.
ちょっと締めてて
I don't like it.
嫌だ
This is amazing.
すごいよこれ
Let's look at that naughty pussy from a different angle.
そのエッチなおまんこさ、 違う角度から見ようかな
Maybe a different angle.
違う角度かな
There he was, kneeling down on all fours.
そこに、 膝ついて四つんばいみたいになってる
Yes, look over there.
そう、あっち向いて
Pull up your pants and skirt by yourself.
自分でパンツを スカート上げて
yes.
そう
So, lean over there.
で、あっちに寄っかかって
Have your ass stuck out.
ケツ突き出してもらう
oh yeah.
そうそう
Ah, this is a spectacular view.
あ、これ絶景だわ
Yuki-chan, look this way.
ゆきちゃんこっち向いて
yes.
そう
Look this way.
こっち向いてごらん
Not yet.
まだダメ
Let's make Yukichanbori one move.
一手、 ゆきちゃんぼりさせよう
Hold your butt with your hands and say "Gaba".
手でさ、 自分のお尻を持って、 ガバっていう
Show me everything.
全部見せつけてごらん
With both hands.
両手で両手で
difficult.
難しい
Super embarrassing.
超恥ずかしいやつ
Just something.
ちょっと何か
I just can't do it.
ちょっとできない
It's done.
できてるよ
Just turn this way.
そのままこっち向いて
Don't show your face.
顔を映しない
Look at the camera.
カメラ見てごらん
A lot of embarrassing things.
い っぱい恥ずかしいやつ
Are you going to hide your butt?
お尻隠しちゃうの?
No good, I'll hide my butt.
ダメじゃん、お尻隠しちゃう
Hoglan was in a naughty place.
エッチなとこにホグランのあってました
No, that's right.
いや、そうなんですよ
You're doing really well.
すっごいよくしてますね
sorry.
ごめんなさい
So please sit down right away.
じゃあすぐに座ってごらん
This cute face is also irresistible after injections.
この可愛い顔も 注射でたまらないでしょ
I want to.
したいね
Please stand up.
立ってごらん
Okay then, Kyo-chan.
じゃあ いいよ、きょうちゃん
Give me your support.
応援あげろ
Can I do that?
していい?
nice.
いい ね
The face giving the injection is cute.
注射してる顔可愛い
What do you think, Pro-chan?
どう、プロちゃん?
Highest.
最高
What about your lips?
唇は?
Highest?
最高?
It's really nice.
すっごいいいね
Yuki-chan, don't say anything.
ゆきちゃん、ベロベーってなして
Beloved.
ベロベーって
Pro-chan, are you there?
プロちゃん、そこなの?
Beloved.
ベロベーって
What about the third tuner John?
どう、3人目のチューナージョン?
It smells good.
いい匂いがする
It smells nice.
いい 匂 いがする
Pro-chan, when that happens.
プロちゃん、そんなときには
Out again.
もう一回、出
Get out, get out.
出ーって出して
It doesn't come out.
出ない
If he doesn't show up, I'm going to rush into Pro-chan already.
出ないんだったら、もうプロちゃん突っ込んじゃう
They're all seated.
全部座れちゃってるね
It's good to fill your mouth.
口の中いっぱいいいでしょ
This is cute and great.
これは可愛くて偉いな
Yeah, amazing.
うん、すごい
It was really cool.
まにしかったね
Not here.
ここじゃないっすね
Chikubi and tsuntsun.
チクビ出してツンツンして
If you stand up, I'll lick you.
立ってきたら舐めちゃうよ
I'll sit down.
座るよ
copper?
どう?
Chikubi is being searched.
チクビ探られて
It's so embarrassing.
めっちゃ恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
I took some.
ちょっと取ってきたね
Cute breasts.
可愛いおっぱい
Chew me.
チューしてくれ
Please lick me a lot.
いっぱい舐めてくれ
delicious.
おいしい
Chikubipin, it's all wet.
チクビピン、びしゃびしゃになっちゃってるよ
Being licked by someone.
どっちかに舐められて
Yuki-chan.
ゆきちゃん
It feels a little good, doesn't it?
ちょっと気持ちいいでしょ
It feels a little good.
ちょっと気持ちいい
Please lick this one too.
こっちも舐めてくれ
Opposite side.
反対側
This one is standing too.
こっちも立ってるね
Are you standing already?
もう立ってるの?
Chikubi, look.
チクビ、見て
My boobs are being licked.
おっぱい舐められてるよ
It's soft.
柔らかいね
Kurushi-chan, I'm going to smear all of those breasts in my mouth.
くるしちゃん、そのおっぱい全部口に塗りちゃう
On the other hand, I also lick her breasts.
反対もおっぱい舐める
soft.
柔らかい
I have been licked violently.
激しく舐められてきた
You won't lick it, will you?
舐めないでしょ
Yuki-chan, you licked me in an embarrassing place.
ゆ きちゃん、恥ずかしいところに舐めたのよ
On the side.
脇のところ
I've been licked before.
舐められたことある
On the side.
脇のところ
I'm sweating.
汗かいてる
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
I'm not sweating much.
あんまり汗かいてない
I'll lick it all.
全部舐めちゃう
No way.
いやー
amazing.
すごい
Are you feeling nervous?
ニュルニュルしてる?
Kurushi-chan, wet your shirt.
くるしちゃん、シャツ濡らして
I agree.
そうだね
I'll take brown.
ブラウン取っちゃいますね
Your breasts are delicious, Kurushi-chan.
おっぱい美味しいでしょ、くるしちゃん
Amazing teeth game.
すごい歯ごっこ
It's soft.
柔らかいし
I'm going to lick this side too.
こっちの脇も舐めちゃう
There is no such thing.
なんてないでしょ
I'll wipe my sweat.
汗拭いちゃう
After I wipe my sweat, I'll lick this too.
汗拭いたらこっちも舐めちゃう
It doesn't taste like it at all.
全然味しないよ
It's a little damp.
ちょっと湿ってる
I licked it all.
全部舐めたのよ
Look this way.
こっち向いてごらん
Keep facing this way.
こっち向いたまま
terrible.
やばい
It feels weird.
変な感じ
You're doing something embarrassing.
恥ずかしいことしてるね
I got my sweaty armpits licked.
汗かいた脇舐められちゃったね
Turn to me and show me your embarrassed face.
こっち向いて恥ずかしい顔見せてくれ
Because it's cute.
可愛いんだから
Kurushi-chan.
くるしちゃん
I can't stand this.
たまんないね、これ
This cuteness.
この可愛さ
Kurushi-chan, you've already cried comfortably, haven't you?
くるしちゃん、もう気持ちよく泣いたんじゃね?
I cried.
泣いた
Hey.
ねえ
How can you lick my armpits?
どうやって脇舐められるの?
I worked hard on it.
つくづくした
I was embarrassed.
恥ずかしがってた
close.
近い
Kurushi-chan, come here.
くるしちゃん、こっちおいで
Yuki-chan, sit down.
ゆきちゃん、座って
Yuki-chan.
ゆきちゃん
What is this?
これ何?
What is it?
なんだろう?
I don't understand.
分かんないよね
What if this black thing covered me?
この黒いのに覆われちゃったら
this is...
これは...
pants.
パンツ
Are these pants?
これはパンツ?
What is that?
それは何?
paper inside.
中身の紙
Let's take a look inside and guess what it is.
中身で見てみて何か当ててみようか
Take off your pants slowly.
パンツをゆっくり脱がして
Easy to see.
見やすい
Check what's inside.
中に何あるか確認して
What are you laughing at?
何が笑ってんの?
What do you think there is?
何あると思ってんの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
Look ahead.
前見て
Have you seen it before?
前見た?
this.
これ
What is this?
何これ?
Have you seen it yet?
もう見てんの?
this is...
これは...
what?
何ですか?
Chincheng.
チンチェン
That's correct.
正解です
I understand.
よく分かったね
There's a penis under the pants.
パンツの下にチンチェンあるって
What did you find out?
どこが分かった?
what?
何?
How do you see this?
どう見てこれ?
How does it make you feel?
ど んな気分になる?
That's naughty.
エッチですね
Feeling naughty?
エッチな気分になる?
Try touching the tip.
先っぽつんつん触ってみて
Touch me steadily.
つんつん触って
The tip feels good.
先っぽ気持ちいいんだよ
As for the man.
男の人は
this?
これ?
Touch it as much as you can with your fingers.
いっぱい指でいっぱい触ってごらん
Various places.
いろんなところ
full?
いっぱい?
Try touching it by chance.
たまたまとかも触ってごらん
Have you ever touched it?
触ったことある?
No, I won't touch it.
いや、触らないの
Touch it.
触ってごらん
What does it feel like?
どんな感じか
Because it looks painful.
痛そうだから
It doesn't hurt.
痛くないよ
Kuru-chan feels so good.
くるちゃん気持ちいいよな
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいい
Now, hold it in your hand.
じゃあ、 手で持ってごらん
At the stick.
棒のところで
Move it a little and make the penis bigger.
それをちょっと動かして、 ちんちん大きくしてごらん
By yourself.
自分で
Looks like a huge dick.
すごいちんちんみたい
It hurts if you squeeze it too hard.
強く握ったら痛いんだよ
You can hold it tight.
強く握っていいよ
Isn't it getting bigger?
なんか大きくなってきてない?
Look carefully.
よく見てごらん
Nearby.
近くに
Look.
ほら
Hasn't something evolved?
なんか進化してない?
It has evolved a bit.
ちょっと 進化した
It has evolved.
進化しちゃったね
Is it like this?
こんな感じかな?
Kuru-chan, that stings my face.
くるちゃん、それ顔につんつんして
This cute face.
この可愛い顔
Shin-chan, guess.
しんちゃん、当ててみ
Have you ever guessed?
当てられたことある?
No, not really.
いや、あまり
This is also my first experience.
これも初体験だ
Kuru-chan, this is the best.
くるちゃん、これは最高だわ
For such a cute child.
こんな可愛い子に
Do something disgusting.
嫌らしいことして
It's hard and somehow bounces back.
固くてなんか弾き返されてる
Isn't it that hard?
そんなに固いんじゃない?
Just smell it.
ちょっとそれ匂い嗅いでみ
What kind of smell?
どんな匂い?
Odorless.
無臭
Good thing you're a clean person.
良 かったね、清潔な人で
Stare at it, that.
ちんちん見つめて、それ
Let's take a quick look.
さっきっぽに、ちゅーしよう
So cute.
すげー可愛い
Just leave it on for a while.
ちょっと、ちゅーつけっぱなし
Leave it on.
つけっぱなし
Chin-chan is cute even if you guess.
ちんちゃん、当てられても可愛いよ
Then, take out your tongue.
そ したら、ベロ出して
Belovero.
ベロベロって
Try licking it little by little.
ちょっとずつ舐めてみ
What does it taste like?
どんな味する?
I don't taste it.
味しない
Then, try licking it more.
じゃあ、もっといっぱい舐めてみ
Give me a lot of tongue.
ベロいっぱい出して
I was just saying that too.
さっきもベロんってして
amazing.
すごい
I'm not used to licking that much.
あんまり舐め慣れてないね
difficult.
難しい
That's amazing, that
すごいね、それ
but.
が
I want to lick everything around this spot.
この カリのところ、周り全部舐めたい
Around.
周り
All around the area just now.
さっきっぽの周り全部
I want to lick it all.
全部舐めたい
Clean it.
きれいにして
Was it jiggly?
ぷるぷるした?
picture?
え?
Was it jiggly?
ぷるぷるした?
is that so.
そうですか
Next time, please lick it.
次さ、 たまたま、 舐めてください
Chinch up.
チンチを上に上げて
Does this hurt?
これ痛い?
Please lick it.
舐めてください
It's licking from below.
下からベロベロって
From the bottom to the top.
下から、 上までベロって
From chance to the tip of the chinch.
たまたまから、 チンチの先っぽまで
Please lick all the way to the top.
上まで舐めてください
once again.
もう一度
Give me more tongue.
もっとベロを出して
Hit me a lot.
いっぱいつぶつけて
It's difficult.
むずい
Give me more tongue
もっとベロを出して
please.
ください
Guru-chan, what do you think?
グ ルちゃん、どう?
Will you open your mouth and let it eat you?
口を開いて、 それを食われちゃうの?
Chinch.
チンチ
While sucking dick.
チンチを吸いながら
inhale?
吸う?
If I do more,
もっといっぱいやったら、
Oh no, no.
や めちゃダメ
too
も
To the back
っと 奥
Please enter up to .
まで 入れてください
Chinch all the inside of your mouth.
口の中を全部チンチにしてください
You can do it.
できるじゃん
Have you ever gone this deep?
こんな奥まで入れたことある?
I'll go in more.
もっと入るよ
Then, put a spit on it and tease the tip with your hand.
そしたら、 ツバつけて、 手で先っぽいじめてください
Please touch the tip with your hand.
手で先っぽいっぱいじってください
oh yeah.
そうそう
Make it slimy.
ぬるぬるにしてさ
Wear a lot of that.
それいっぱいつけて
Hold it better.
もっとちゃんと持って
Make yourself feel good.
気持ちよくして
Rub it a lot.
いっぱいこすって
It's difficult.
むずい
Faster.
もっと早く
Spit on it.
ツバがつく
Try pushing harder.
もっと強くいってみ
Tightly.
しこしこっと
Yes, sooner.
そう、もっと早く
Look, it's getting harder and harder.
ほら、どんどん硬くなってきた
It's getting early, isn't it?
早くなってきたでしょ?
Ahead, with a bang.
先、パンパンで
Koko-chan feels good, right?
ここちゃん気持ちいいでしょ?
Move more.
もっと動かして
copper?
どう?
it hurts?
痛い?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It feels good.
気持ちいいよな
I'll eat that.
それ食べちゃう
So cute.
すごいかわいい
Come over here.
こっち向いてこら
While facing the camera.
カメラ向きながら
Move quickly.
早く動かして
Chipotchipo quickly.
ちぽちぽって早く
hand?
手?
mouth.
口
Because it feels good.
それ気持ちいいから
Please move faster.
もっと早く動かしてこら
Make a clicking sound.
ちぽちぽって音出して
yes.
そう
Isn't it good?
うまいでしょ?
Let's make you feel even better.
も っと気持ちよくしてあげな
You like it when men feel good, right?
男の人気持ちよくなるの好きでしょ?
Don't you know?
わかんない?
I'm going to do my best.
一生懸命ちんちんなる
Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃん
Hold Yuki-chan's head.
ゆきちゃんの頭持って
Yuki-chan, open your mouth.
ゆきちゃん口開けて
Kuro-chan, turn to me.
黒ちゃん向いてこら
cute.
かわいい
I'm going to drive in.
ちんちん打ち込んじゃう
Yuki-chan suck more and make more noise.
ゆきちゃんもっといっぱい吸って音出して
Kuro-chan shakes her hips a lot.
黒ちゃんいっぱい腰振って
I'll put it in my mouth.
口に入れちゃう
I'll go deeper.
もっと奥まで入れちゃう
I want you to lick me more.
もっと舐めてもらえる
Head with both hands.
両手で頭
I felt so much better.
すんごい気持ちよくなった
Just smoke it, and smoke it even more.
そのまま吸ってもっともっと吸いな
Chin chin.
ち んちん
Make lots of noise.
いっぱい音出して
I'm going to put Kuro-chan deep inside.
黒ちゃん一番奥まで入れちゃう
To the point where it hurts.
苦しいところまで
painful.
苦しい
Can you bear with me even when it's painful?
苦しいところも我慢してもらえんか
I can't.
できない
Just once.
一 回だけ
It went really deep.
すんごい奥まで入ったね
One more time.
もう一回
Give me more tongue.
ベロもっと出して
Make it all wet.
びちゃびちゃにして
Hold a lot of tongue.
結構いっぱいベロを持って
It looks like it's going to turn.
回りそう
Lick it in your mouth at the end.
最後口に舐めて
One more time.
もう一回
Feel good.
気持ちよく
Suck it and see.
吸ってほら
Look here.
こっち見な
This feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょこれ
If you lick me more, I'll go to bed, Kuro-chan.
もっと舐めてもらえたら ベット行くから黒ちゃん
Let's do that.
そうしよう
Burki-chan this is dick.
ブルキちゃんこれちんちん
It's gotten so big.
こんなでっかくなっちゃって
You're feeling a bit like Ichi, aren't you?
ちょっと一の気分になったでしょ
Then I'll go to bed.
じゃあベット行くよ
Come on, come on.
おいでほら
Then I happened to lick it again.
そしたらもう一回たまたまから舐めて
Lick it all the way to the top.
上まで全部舐めて
Please make it bigger again.
また一本大きくしてあげて
superior?
上?
It's all the way to the top.
上までだよ
Let's touch the tip as much as possible.
先っぽいっぱいチロチロしよう
Don't eat there.
そこは食べちゃいばく
Suck it deliciously
うまみたく吸っていっぱ
stomach.
い
You can eat and drink a lot.
い っぱい飲食してもいい
I'll have it done sooner and later.
それだんだん早くしてもらう
Have them hold a huge amount in their hands.
すごい量を手で持ってもらう
It's getting bigger.
大きくなってきたね
Yeah.
うん
amazing
すごい
hey.
ね
I'm doing a lot of jopojopo while looking at this.
こ っち見ながらいっぱいジョポジョポしてる
I'm surprised.
びっくりしてる
I keep playing Jopojopo without stopping.
やめないでずっとジョポジョポしてる
While using my hands a lot.
手もいっぱい使いながら
Hold it tight.
ぎゅっと持って
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
It definitely feels good.
気持ちいいよ絶対
Please drink a lot of that soon.
それいっぱい早く飲んであげな
quickly?
早く?
Nice, spit on me a lot.
いいね、いっぱいつば出て
Have them covered in spittle.
も っとつばだらけにしてもらう
I get teased a lot.
いっぱい先っぽいじめてもらう
Make it feel good.
気持ちいいになってもらう
As soon as possible.
い っぱい早く
Faster.
もっと早く
Use your hands a lot.
手もいっぱい使って
Hold it tight.
ぎゅっと持って
Okay?
いい そう?
oh yeah.
そうそう
Have them face this way.
こっち向いてもらう
I can't put it all in.
いっぱい入れない
I'm so energetic
こんなに元気
It has become.
にな っちゃったじゃん
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Speak loud and clear one last time.
もう一回最後もういっきり喋って
Jopojopo.
ジョポジョポ
quickly.
早く
Come on first.
一番早くほら
More and more.
もっともっと
That feels so good.
それすごい気持ちいい
It's gotten so much better.
すごい良くなっちゃったね
Kuro-chan then woke up.
黒ちゃんそしたら起きて
Next time Kuro-chan.
今度黒ちゃん
Yuki-chan, feel good.
ゆきちゃん気持ちよくしな
free
自由
from.
から
Don't cancel.
中 止な
The two of us, involving Pero more.
もっとペロ絡めて2人で
Yuki-chan, go to sleep.
ゆきちゃん寝てほら
Goronte hora.
ごろんてほら
Go to sleep.
寝てほら
Kuro-chan, let's lick this breast again.
黒ちゃんまたこれおっぱいなめちゃ
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
bright.
明るい
bright?
明るい?
It's bright so everything is lit up.
明るいから全部つってるよ
Her breasts might be licked.
おっぱいなめられてるかも
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Come down even more.
もっといっぱい下出して
Licking it licking it.
ペロペロなめちゃ
It feels good, right?
やっぱ気持ちいいでしょ?
Licked.
なめられた
Hey.
ねえ
Pleasant breasts.
気持ちいいおっぱい
Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃん
Here, here.
ここなめちゃ、ここ
I felt embarrassed for a while.
しばらく恥ずかしいと
You have to see it.
見なきゃねえよ
My hands are pounding.
手ドキて
手ドキな
dirty.
汚い
Isn't it dirty?
汚くない?
Take a lot.
いっぱい取る
dirty.
汚い
Hands get in the way.
手邪魔
No.
ダメ
It's so beautiful.
すごいきれいじゃん
No.
ダメ
Kuro-chan, make a chestnut.
黒ちゃん、栗にちゅうしちゃえ
No.
ダメ
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょよ
Put it in your tongue hole.
ベロ穴に入れちゃえ
To the very back.
ちばん奥まで
Put more in.
もっと入れて
It might feel good.
気持ちいいかも
My pussy is being thrown.
マンコ投げられてる
Let me look at this.
こっち見てもらう
It makes me lick it even harder.
もっと激しくベロベロってなっちゃう
Everything from the bottom.
下から全部
Everything is being thrown.
全部投げられてる
Your face looks nice.
顔が気持ちいい顔になってるじゃん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
This was taken.
これ取られてね
Kuro-chan, what do you think?
黒ちゃん、どう?
Pussy feet.
マンコの足
delicious.
おいしい
Look at this face.
顔見てみ、これ
This cute pussy.
こんなかわいいこのマンコ
So cute.
すごいかわいい
I need to suck more.
もっといっぱいしゃぶんないと
Should I suck it as much as possible?
い っぱいしゃぶったらいいの?
Yeah.
うん
There's a lot in it.
すんごい入ってんじゃん
Hey.
ねえ
I need to see it more.
もっと眺めさせないと
vice versa.
逆に
A very erotic face.
すんごいエロい顔が
Kuro-chan, put your finger on it slowly and put your finger in it.
黒ちゃん、つばつけでゆっくり指入れてこらん
This is tough.
これきつい
きついよ、これは
Because it's definitely small.
絶対ちっちゃいから
Look, this is in there.
見て、これ入ってんの
Is everything included?
全部入っちゃってる?
Yeah.
うん
More, look.
つもっと、ほら
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
Did you put your finger in?
指入んの
I played around with the comfortable part above.
上の気持ちいいとこいっぱいいじったんよ
Yeah.
うん
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
This is so naughty.
すごいエッチだ、これ
That makes me sneeze a lot.
あれがよくあくしちゃう
No pussy showing
まんこ見せなき
Yeah.
ゃ
Kurimo also licks it.
く りもペロペロなめてくるじゃん
The one you put your finger in
指入れたほう
but.
が
I licked it a lot.
い っぱいなめたんよ
Just leave it there.
そのままで、ほら
Because my pussy is being licked.
まんこなめられてるから
That's difficult.
難しいね
It's suitable for this way.
こっち向きなの
A pleasant face.
気持ちいい顔
It's getting bigger.
くり大きくなってきたよ
It's starting to dawn.
くり立ってきたよ
Hey.
ねえ
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Stand up.
立っちゃって
Make it feel good with your fingers.
指で気持ちよくしてほら
Come on, fall.
ほら、落ちて
Look further up.
もっと上についてほら
My pussy twitches.
まんこ、ひくひくして
It's cute, come on.
かわいいね、ほら
Just put your finger in this thing and see.
こいつに指だけ入れてほら
Come in, fall.
入って、落ちて
Open your legs.
足開けな
Tease me, Gao-chan.
いじめて、ガオちゃん
You put your finger in it.
指入れられちゃったね
Rub it harder, Gao-chan.
もっと上こすってほら、ガオちゃん
Look, you're starting to look nice.
ほら、気持ちいい顔になってきた
He's patient with me.
我慢してくれてる
hot water
ゆ
Ki-chan, can I use your special secret liquid?
き ちゃん、とっておきな秘密液使っていい?
Right.
じゃん
Embark.
エンバーク
I'll open it gently.
優しく開けてあげる
He's patient with me.
我慢してくれてる
Do you enjoy this sound?
この音が楽しい?
It's fun, huh
楽しいね、ほ
and others.
ら
Yuki-chan, isn't it okay?
ゆ きちゃん、いいでしょ?
Isn't it okay to be jumpy?
びくびくしてもいいんじゃないの?
No, no.
ダメ、ダメ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
patience.
我慢
Don't go into it.
にもいちゃダメ
The system is in place.
仕組みも立ってるし
Can I be nervous?
しびくびくしてもいい?
No, no.
ダメ、ダメ
ダ メ、ダメ
Couldn't resist?
我慢できなかったの?
No, hold on.
いけない、我慢
This got wet.
これ濡れちゃったよ
Stop it again.
もう 一回、やめて
I'll make it beautiful.
綺麗にしちゃう
It's so wet.
すごい濡れてる
Put everything inside.
中まで全部入れて
Notice, Pelope
気づいて、ペロペ
B.
ロ
How are you being teased so much?
どう こんなに舐められてる?
How do you feel?
どういう気分?
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
It's embarrassing though.
恥ずかしいけど
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
Give me more licks at the end.
もっといっぱい最後に舐めて
Take out a lot of pussy.
いっぱいマンコン出して
Don't put the bottom in either.
下も入れちゃいけません
Stir everything inside the mancon.
マンコンの中全部かき回して
You want to include that, right?
それ入れたいでしょ?
I want to put it in.
入れたい
Yuuki-chan, please lick me.
ゆうきちゃん、舐めてください
Go up.
上に行って
Kuro-chan also shook her hips.
くろちゃんも腰を振って
Open your legs.
足を開いて
Don't show me your pussy.
マンコン見せないで
Kuro-chan, come on.
くろちゃん、おいで
Because it's tough.
きっついから
Looks small.
狭そう
It seems narrow.
狭 そうだ ね
The child who is going home is also cute.
ちんちん帰ってる子もかわいいよ
Look at this too.
こっちも見て
Look, I'm going to sleep really well.
ほら、すーごい寝る寝る
While opening your legs.
足開きながら
Don't leave it there and show it.
入 っておいて見せないで
Kuro-chan, run like this.
くろちゃん、こうやって走れ
I don't mind going deep into it though.
一番奥ついてもいいけどね
You can do it faster.
上に早くしてもいい
Yuuki-chan, it's okay to make your throat feel better.
ゆうきちゃん、喉気持ちよくしてもいい
You can also take a look at this.
こ っちも見てもいい
You look like you're feeling really good.
すごい気持ちよさそうな顔してる
Your eyes are so wet.
すごい濡れ濡れな目をま
I'm sorry.
わ る
My penis is so shiny.
すごいちんちんテカテカしてる
Let's laugh comfortably.
気持ちよく笑おう
Let me feel your big penis.
でっかいちんちんいっぱい感じてもらおう
Take it and fill it up.
持っていっぱい入れな
courage
ゆうき
Chan, you're gone.
ちゃん、 行っちゃったね
Yuki-chan,
ゆ うきちゃん、
Have them move their hips forward and backward like this.
前 と後ろにこうやって腰を動かしてもらおう
can?
できる?
I can't.
できないね
Well then, let's ask Kuro-chan to follow me.
じゃあ、くろちゃんについてもらいな
Chew Kuro-chan yourself.
くろちゃんにチューしてごらん、自分から
So, Kuro-chan shook his dick a lot.
で、 くろちゃんはちんちんいっぱい振って
Take a look here too.
こっちも見てごらん
It's there, so fill it up.
入ってるからいっぱいにして
Please stay tuned.
ずっとチューしててね
Kuro-chan is hugging me.
くろちゃんにぎゅーってして
There were a lot of them.
い っぱいついたんだ
Yuuki-chan looks like her pussy is full.
ゆうきちゃん、まんこズボズボ入ってるような
It's like I'm taking everything.
全部取ってるような
As far as the butt hole.
お尻の穴までは
That's amazing, Kuro-chan.
すごい、くろちゃん
Good day, Chinchin
き ょうきいね、ちんちん
hey.
ね
Look at me, show me your face.
こ っちも見て、見せてごらん、顔
cute face
かわいい顔
So cute.
すごいかわいい
Kuro-chan, I want to see more of Yuuki-chan's pleasant face.
くろちゃん、もっとゆうきちゃんの気持ちいい顔見たいから
Have them follow you a lot.
い っぱいついてもらう
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
You look so comfortable.
すごい気持ちいい顔してるわ
Show me a lot of pakopaco.
いっぱいパコパコ見せて
I'll have a lot of them.
いっぱいついてもらう
No matter when you are there
い っぱ いつ いて も ら
cormorant.
う
Go all the way to the bottom.
一 番奥までついて
Yuuki-chan, let's do something that feels more comfortable.
ゆうきちゃん、もっと気持ちいいやつやってあげようか
She has a really erotic face.
すんごいエロい顔になってるよ
Look towards the wind.
風向いてごらん
Your pussy is so wet.
すごいおまんこびしょびしょだよ
Soaked.
びしょびしょ
Something naughty silver.
なんかエッチなシルバー
Yuuki-chan came out because it felt good.
ゆうきちゃんが気持ちいいから出たんだよ
Yuki-chan came out because it felt good.
ゆ うきちゃん気持ちいいから出たんだよ
That's amazing.
すごいね
It feels amazing.
すごい 気持ちよさそうだな
Kuro-chan, don't worry about your head.
くろちゃん、頭あっちゃおらん
Yuuki-chan, I'm going to do a really naughty pose from now on.
ゆうきちゃん、今からすごいエッチなポーズするから
Look at this for yourself.
見てこれ、自分で
Yuuki-chan's buns.
ゆうきちゃんのまんじゅう
The one that came out of here.
ここから出たやつ
Yuuki-chan's buns.
ゆうきちゃんのまんじゅう
That's amazing.
すごい ね
Look, it's silver.
ほら、シルバーしちゃったね
Wait again, at the letter M.
またまって、M字で
behind.
後ろ
Put your hands behind your back.
後ろに手をつく
Get on top of Kuro-chan.
くろちゃんのところに乗っかって
Make it look like an M.
M字みたいにして
Put your feet up.
足立てて
About Oshireishi and Kuro-chan.
おしれいし、くろちゃんについて
Please stand up.
足立ててごらん
So let's put this in.
それでこれ、入れてごらん
By yourself.
自分で
Stay behind me.
後ろついてて
So, lift your hips.
で、腰を浮かして
This is so naughty.
すごいエッチだよ、これ
Do you know it's all the way inside?
奥まで入ってるのわかる?
You understand, right?
わかるでしょ?
Kuro-chan, it's still slow.
くろちゃん、まだゆっくりだよ
Taste the pussy to the fullest.
まんこいっぱい味わってごらん
This is tough, isn't it?
きついでしょ、これ
Pussy.
まんこね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It feels good.
気 持ちいいね
Kuro-chan, please hurry up.
くろちゃん、どんどん早くしてごらん
More, more, more, more.
もっと、もっと、もっと、もっと
A lot of bears.
いっぱいまくまやついて
Kuro-chan, look further.
くろちゃん、もっと、ほら
Please stick around.
い っぱいついてごらん
Her face has become very cute.
すごいかわいい顔になってきた
Are you going?
いっちゃうの?
Come closer.
寄りしてみろ
Hey, look.
ちょっと、ほら
This thing is soaking wet.
びしょびしょだよ、これ
Chin chin.
ちんちん
It feels really good.
本当に気持ちいいんだね
It's all the way inside.
奥までずぼずぼ入ってる
Kuro-chan, please follow me again.
くろちゃん、もう一回ついてごらん
Let's keep it going.
連続でいかせよう
Kuro-chan, you can't take a break.
くろちゃん、休んじゃダメだよ
Because it feels so good.
こんな気持ちいいんだから
More and more.
もっと、いっぱいついて
Her pussy was filled up.
まんちゅういっぱいされていった
I'm gone again.
また、いっちゃった
Yuki-chan, erotic.
ゆきちゃん、エロ
Erotic, Yuki-chan.
エロい、ゆきちゃん
Well then, take it out.
じゃあ、抜いてごらん
Come forward.
前にきて
Take out all the stickers.
シールいっぱい出してごらん
It's dangerous.
やばいですよ
She's a perverted pussy.
変態マン子だね
Huh, what is it?
え、なんだろう?
Kuro-chan, come behind me.
くろちゃん、後ろにきて
Follow me from behind.
後ろからついてごらん
It's embarrassing.
恥 ず かしい
It's not dirty.
汚くないよ
I would be so excited if I became Yuki-chan.
ゆきちゃんになったら、超きるよ
No, no, no, no.
いや、ダメ、ダメ、ダメです
dirty.
汚い
Lick the sticker.
シール、なめてごらん
Okay, lick it all.
いいよ、全部なめてごらん
dirty.
汚い
It's embarrassing, a lot.
恥ずかしいね、いっぱい
Kuro-chan, follow me again.
くろちゃん、もう一回ついて
Full of manchu.
まんちゅういっぱい
Because it feels better.
気 持ちよくなったから
While looking at me.
こっち見ながら
Chin Chin, show me something like Rial.
チンチン、リュアルとか見せなさい
copper?
どう?
Text by Kuro-chan and Yuki-chan.
くろちゃん、ゆきちゃんの文
Oh, that's great.
ああ、最高
I can't see it, but it's probably dripping again.
見えてないけど、たぶんまた汁垂れてるよ、
full.
いっぱい
What?
なんだ?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Let's do some more banging, Kuro-chan.
もっとパンパンしようかな、くろちゃん
Does that feel good?
それ気持ちいいの?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Kuro-chan at max speed.
くろちゃん、マックススピードで
Kuro-chan, I'll just follow you.
くろちゃん、そのままついちゃう
I'll deliver it to the deepest part, Kuro-chan.
一番奥に届けるね、くろちゃん
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Shall we go again?
また行っちゃう?
Kuro-chan, hold your arm.
くろちゃん、腕を持ってごらん
Let me show you how it works and where it goes.
仕組みを見せながら行くところを見せてごらん
You're dripping a lot of juice, Yuki-chan.
いっぱい汁垂れてるもんね、ゆきちゃん
It feels good inside.
奥気持ちいいんだ
Kuro-chan, the deepest one.
くろちゃん、一番奥
Look.
ほら
So so so so so so so so so such.
そこそこそこ
Not yet.
まだまだ
Kuro-chan, let me go further.
くろちゃん、もっと行かせて
Ho
ほ
and others.
ら
My lower back is twitching like this.
腰、 こんなビクビクしちゃって
My pussy is in this state.
マンコ、こういう状態になってる
Sleep until the end.
最後まで寝て
Full of juice.
汁いっぱい
Lots of stains.
しみがいっぱい
Snow soup, snow soup.
ゆき汁、ゆき汁
It's Yukijiru.
ゆき汁だよ
Slowly from the opening to the roots.
あきっぽから根元までゆっくり
You're in.
お前、入ってる
Bad.
悪め
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Even if I go too far, I'll go right away, like I did earlier.
行きすぎてもすぐ行っちゃうね、さっきからね
It's still slow, slow.
まだゆっくりだよ、ゆっくり
If you feel comfortable even if it's slowly,
ゆっくりでも気持ちいい状態になってたら、
Please get it done sooner and later.
だ んだん早くしてもらって
No.
ダメ
I'll take your face wherever you go.
行くところの顔、取ってあげる
No.
ダメ
Think about your penis.
ちんちんのことで考えろ
Think about what feels good.
気持ちいいことで考えろ
It's hitting the deep end.
奥当たってる
Are you hitting the nail on the head?
奥当たってる?
I'm going to go to the back of the house.
奥当たって行っちゃうもんな
Kuro-chan, come on, come all the way.
クロちゃん、ほら奥いっぱいついて
No, no, no.
ダメ、ダメ、ダメ
Go wherever you go.
行くところにしてみろ
It's in the back, Kuro-chan.
一番奥だよ、クロちゃん
So cute.
すごいかわいい
I'll go right away.
すぐ行っちゃうね
I can't stand it.
我慢できない
Let's go to the end.
もっと最後に行かせよう
I can't hide my boobs.
おっぱい隠せない
Take lots of cute faces.
可愛い顔いっぱい取る
No.
ダ メ
Kuro-chan,
クロちゃん、
Please cum already.
もう 中出して
No.
ダメ
No medium?
中ダメ?
Cum inside me.
中出して
Go deeper, see.
一番奥ついて、ほら
Let me go.
行 かせてから
Yuki-chan, let me go last.
ゆきちゃん、最後に行かせて
Lots of them.
いっぱいついて
Let me go.
行かせて
Kuro-chan, be the first.
クロちゃん、一番早く
The deepest one.
一番奥ついて
Yuki-chan, let me go last.
ゆきちゃん、最後に行かせて
I'll go again.
また行っちゃう
I can't stand it.
我慢できない
Kuro-chan, the last one.
クロちゃん、最後
Give me a lot.
いっぱい出して
go.
行く
Deepest.
一番奥
Write it down from the inside.
中から書き出して
Put your finger inside.
中、指入れて
Did it go too far inside?
奥に出すぎたか
It came out.
出てきた
Look at that cute face.
見て、この可愛い顔
You gave it all out, right?
全部出しちゃったでしょ
Yuki-chan might get mad at me.
ゆきちゃんに怒られちゃうかも
He said he was hungry.
お腹いなすって言った
Yuki-chan, you should cum inside me.
ゆきちゃん、中出したほうが
It's also crunchy here.
ここもビシャビシャ
Yuki-chan, wake up.
ゆきちゃん、起きてこな
At the end, Yuki-chan's manjul is sticky.
最後は、ゆきちゃんのマンジュルでベタベタだ
I'll make it beautiful.
綺麗にしちゃうよな
Look and clean.
見て、掃除して
That's amazing.
すごいね
It's Yuki-chan's.
ゆきちゃんのだよ
I don't lick it myself.
自分で舐めないんだよ
I don't lick it.
舐めない
So I have to clean it up.
だから、綺麗にしないと
A carrot bigger than your face.
顔より大きい人参
Lick it a lot.
いっぱい舐めて
I happen to have it here.
たまたま、ここに置いてるよ
Park from the tip again.
もう一回、先っぽからパークって
It's about at the very back.
一番奥前くらいだよ
Kuro-chan is also good.
黒ちゃんも上手いよ
I wish I could take a break further in the back.
もっと奥前、休憩してもらえたら
Was it beautifully done?
綺麗にできた?
TRUE?
本当?
Isn't it enough?
足りないんじゃない?
It's one more time.
もう一回だよ
One more time.
もう一回
Kuro-chan is beautiful.
黒ちゃん、綺麗
Another dick.
もうちんちん
Not enough?
足りない?
I guess it's not enough.
足りないんだろう
copper?
どう?
Has it become beautiful?
綺麗になった?
It's beautiful now.
綺麗になったね
Yuki-chan.
ゆきちゃん
You said a lot.
いっぱい言ってたね
Hey.
ねえ
You said so many things.
すごいいっぱい言ってたね
It was so cute.
すごい可愛かったよ
I was let out inside though.
中に出されちゃったけど
terrible.
やばい
That's terrible.
やばいな
Yuki-chan is as cute as an idol.
ゆきちゃん、アイドルくらい可愛いからさ
I got excited when I took it.
取ってテンション上がっちゃった
It was so cute.
すんげえ可愛かった
Let's all play together again.
またみんなで遊ぼうよ
See you all again.
またみんなで
Let's play if you have time.
時間あったら遊ぼうよ
Yuki-chan might confess again.
またゆきちゃん告白するかもしれない
No.
ダメです
Thank you for today.
今日はありがとうね
It was fun, though.
楽しかったでしょ、でも
It was just fun.
ほんの楽しかった
bye bye.
バイバイ
see you.
またね
Look here.
こっち見てほら
bye bye.
バイバイ